Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
"Desire the Series"
(Episode 14)
To put it simply
I need to know
if you've been sexually active with a partner lately.
I...
He has.
Congratulations, Mr. Sheng.
Your pheromone imbalance has completely resolved
I'd suggest
that during future rut periods.
You need to continue staying with that same partner.
What?
Your compatibility with that Omega
is likely over 90%.
Their soothing pheromones work especially well for you.
Being intimate helps stabilize your condition.
You're telling my Alpha to sleep with another Omega?
Don't go crazy.
I didn't.
Got it, got it.
If you two are of a minority sexual orientation.
Actually, you could try
using artificially extracted calming pheromones.
Because most patients
with pheromone disorder
will be better
after receiving the solace of this pheromone.
We don't need it.
Mr. Sheng has me.
Mr. Sheng.
Did you hear what Doctor Wang just said?
Yes
I heard that.
He made me have sex with Omega.
Nah.
Lately
Mr. Sheng, besides me.
You haven't had sex with anyone else
or let anyone else comfort you with their pheromones?
Shut up!
Mr. Sheng, are you busy?
Yeah, I'm busy.
Stay away from me.
Trying to get in Mr. Sheng's bed
you can't stay far if that's your goal.
Did I say you could?
You're not invited.
The doctor advised you
to have intimate relations with your partner
Mr. Sheng, are you ignoring the doctor's orders?
The doctor said ‘with Omega'
Are you?
I'm not.
But I want to kiss you.
May I, Mr. Sheng?
I'll step out for a bit.
You don't need to.
Just in case.
What?
Do you think you're dirty?
Mr. Sheng.
Why do you misunderstand me so much?
I haven't touched anyone but you.
Are we going to do it or not?
Why all the fuss?
Well, what if it happens?
Don't blame me.
There's a limit to your madness.
You think I'm an Omega?
Hey
Mr. Sheng.
You finally answered the phone.
I owe my boss over 30 million dollars.
When do you plan to repay it?
Stop fucking nagging me
I lost a fortune at your damn place.
When have I ever missed a payment?
Fine.
You've got three more days.
If you don't pay in time.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Annoying.
Damn it!
No wonder the ancients said governing a nation
is like cooking a small dish.
Who would ever know
the owner of X Holdings
could whip up eggs benedict and avocado toast?
Mr. Hua is quite the homemaker.
Hmm.
I'm not really much of a cook.
To be able to make breakfast for Mr. Sheng,
I studied with a chef for three months.
Such dedication.
Yeah.
What's the reward?
What are you doing?
Just testing our product quality.
X Holdings monopolizes global inhibitor production.
But exploiting that power is unethical.
Mr. Hua
where's your shame?
Mr. Sheng's rut period is approaching.
The first rut cycle post-permanent marking
presents severe separation anxiety symptoms.
You have to be by my side at all times.
Permanent Marking?
You're addicted to acting, aren't you?
Maniac.
Do you have an appointment, sir?
Me, Sheng Shaoqing.
Do I have to make an appointment to come to my office?
I'm sorry, who are you looking for?
Sheng Shaoyou, my elder brother.
Just a moment.
Hello, Secretary Chen
Mr. Sheng Shaoqing is here to see Mr. Sheng.
Uh, Okay
I've asked him to wait.
Please wait over there.
Why delay?
Mr. Hua
Mr. Sheng has been in the lounge for almost two hours.
He's not answering calls or the door
I'll check it out.
This door blocks pheromones.
Yeah, installed last week
Mr. Sheng is an S-Class Alpha.
To protect others during his rut.
We replaced it with an isolation door.
Mr. Sheng.
Hua Yong.
Mr. Sheng, are you there?
Mr. Sheng isn't seeing anyone.
Secretary Chen, mind your place.
What's going on?
My brother hasn't shown up after all this time.
Jokes on me?
I'm sorry
Mr. Sheng is in a meeting.
As soon as the meeting is over
I'll inform him
as soon as he's free.
Big brother.
It's been a long day.
Are you tired from the meetings?
Let me get you a glass of water.
No need.
Get to the point.
Here's the thing.
Brother, I really know I'm wrong.
Please, just one more time.
You embezzled money from the charity fund, didn't you?
No! Absolutely not.
I'm a scumbag, but
I wouldn't touch charity money.
Actually, to be honest
I haven't been in charge over these years.
The Fund's operations.
It's always my secretary handled it.
But.
Funny you mention that.
He left exactly half a month ago.
But don't worry
I'm tracking him down
I'll make it right.
What a coincidence.
The reading room you oversaw
the donation of half a month ago collapsed.
Chen Pinming began investigating the flow of funds.
Your secretary vanished right then.
That's right.
Sheng Shaoqing.
Sheng Shaoqing, just admit you're running from the law.
No charity money was stolen.
Go back and ask your mother.
Let's see if she buys your bullshit.
Brother please!
I'm…I'm sorry
I know I was wrong!
You were right the other day at the hospital
I've been a spoiled brat all these years.
All talk, no skill.
Never accomplished anything
I never pushed myself.
Looking back, I
I've disgraced our father.
And I've failed you.
Brother, please.
Help me.
Just this once, please
I know you.
You're tough on the outside but kind inside.
All these years.
You've been good to our siblings.
Please, I need your help.
Now, for Daddy's sake, will you?
One last favor
I'm begging you.
Like this.
Brother, I
"I swear
I'll never go to the casino again.
If I ever gamble again.
I, Sheng Shaoqing.
He's an animal.
I'm scum.
May I get hit by a car with my mom.
Brother, please
I'm on my knees here.
How much did you lose?
Uh.
Thirty-seven million.
Pathetic.
You're crying over pocket change.
Even your mom's done with you.
She.
I blew through all she gave me.
Bring me the checkbook.
I'll get it.
Never again.
I swear, never again.
Thank you
I swear it won't happen again
I'll get out of your hair.
Call me if you need me.
Where's Hua Yong?
Secretary Hua is there.
Should we call him?
Then you're off the clock.
What about you?
Secretary Hua will drive me.
Yes.
Hua Yong.
Stop lurking.
Give me a hand.
Mr. Sheng can't stand.
How cute.
You got a death wish?
By Mr. Sheng's side
even eternity wouldn't be enough.
Mr. Sheng is good at everything.
But too trusting
I'll have to keep a closer eye.
If anyone tricks him
I'll be heartbroken.
Stop talking nonsense.
I'm tired. Go home.
Hmm.
Weekends are packed.
Shouldn't you rest?
I'm not tired.
Hey.
Brother, brother.
Are you free tomorrow?
What is it?
Nothing urgent.
Just wanted to treat you to dinner.
Not a big deal.
No need for that.
No, no.
Brother, listen.
Hear me out.
This time
I owe you for helping me.
And to celebrate me.
The one who turning over a new leaf.
Just do me a favor, okay?
Hmm.
Got it. Send me the address.
Okay, then.
Who's there?
Sheng Shaoqing.
Asked me to lunch tomorrow.
Well
I'll be right there.
What's going on?
My dad's awake.
Change your clothes.
We'll go to the hospital.
Mr. Sheng, why are you waiting?
Dad.
Coming.
Uncle Sheng.
First time meeting you.
My name is Hua Yong.
Hua Yong.
Shaoyou.
It took me so long to wake up.
Now that I've woken up
you bring friends to visit me.
You must be quite close, hm?
Uncle Sheng.
Mr. Sheng and I are dating.
Dating?
Among JIANGHU's elite families
I don't know any Huas.
Young man.
What's your father's name?
Uncle Sheng, I'm from P
I moved here last year.
My father is dead.
What about your mother?
Gone too.
And who else is in your family?
You just woke up and already interrogating me?
You're not too tired.
You and Hua.
How long has it been going on?
Not long.
It didn't take long for them you to meet the parents.
He's quite young.
Quite the charmer.
You flatter me, Uncle Sheng
I'm who I am
I have my ways.
Okay, I get it.
Uncle Sheng.
You just woke up.
You should rest.
If that's all
Mr. Sheng and I will take our leave now
I'm not tired.
Hua.
Wait outside
I need a word with Shaoyou.
No need.
There's nothing he can't hear.
Mr. Sheng.
It's been a long time since you two talked.
It's the time
I just had a call
I'll wait for you outside.
Mm.
What's wrong?
Yong.
Why aren't you answering my calls?
What's going on?
You've called a dozen times.
This better be important.
Are you in JIANGHU?
Mm.
Meet up?
Are you in JIANGHU too?
Yeah, here with Bea and the kids.
So.
You asked me to be your guide.
You've changed, Yong.
You were always so serious.
You ignored my last call
Chang Yu and Wenlang.
They all told me to contact you directly.
What's going on?
My mom asked you.
Are you coming back to visit P's grave this year?
Uncle, that's your father.
He's been dead for years.
All the family graves.
Have you visited?
Nothing else?
Then I'm hanging up.
No, there's something else I need to ask you.
What?
My anniversary with Bea is soon.
Any gift ideas?
Give her your heart.
Or undying loyalty.
Do you even know loyalty
I'm just not very good at Chinese.
Not illiterate.
Yong, stop dodging the question.
I know people doubt us.
Every month, tabloids say.
Bea and I are splitting up.
Last week Durian Daily also said
I'm the meanest Omega ever.
Lucky to land a clueless Alpha.
Bea's not blind.
They're always talking nonsense.
So what?
The point is you love her to death.
Even had a baby.
Why listen to them?
Oh.
If you really want to make her happy.
Give her another baby.
Another child
would makes her happy?
Yong.
If your partner had a baby for you.
Would you be happy?
Yes.
What a pleasure.
If Auntie can convince Mr. Sheng.
To give me a child
I'll visit the graves at once.
Huh?
That desperate?
Then I see.
Yong.
An anniversary gift is a big deal
I'd like to get your opinion.
Let's meet, shall we?
Are you really that busy?
No.
Not even half an hour?
No time.
That's all.
Done.
What do you think?
He's young.
But shrewd.
Seems
well-bred too.
If you approve
to welcome him in.
I won't stop you.
I do like it.
But I want him to marry int.
Even if you agree.
He may refuse.
You're an S-class Alpha.
Heir to Shengfang Group.
As the Sheng family's matriarch.
Every Omega's dream.
Hua won't do it.
Then he's a fool.
What are you looking at?
See, Baby care is complicated.
It's a bit hard.
Challenging or not?
What's it to you?
You'll need it sooner or later.
Once Mr. Sheng agrees to bear my child.
Dreams have limits
(nonverbal grunt as interjection)
I'm a dreamer.
And I'm good at making dreams come true.
Any cases?
Gon.
You!
To be with Mr. Sheng.
It's my greatest dream.
Did Uncle Sheng discuss me with you just now?
What does he think of me?
Mr. Hua is not only good at dreaming but also good at
communicating inefficiently with older generation.
I do please elders well.
Mm.
He approves of you.
Probably named our future child already.
Hua Sheng
I've been thinking about it since I was sixteen
Mr. Sheng's first child will be named Hua Sheng.
His nickname is Peanut.
You're a dreamer.
Don't you think
it's a perfect name?
The first one is called Hua Sheng.
And the second one?
How about.
What?
Manager Huang.
The driver will take you home
I'll be back after dinner.
Mr. Sheng, I've met your father.
Why leave me behind now
and dine with your future in-law?
Guess I'll starve tonight.
Without me.
I can't get enough to eat.
I hate eating alone
Mr. Sheng, take me with you
I'll be your driver, okay?
They're inviting you to dinner
I'll take you.
Secretary Hua.
Not appropriate, is it?
In Country P, guests don't dictate terms.
I rarely attend dinners in P.
No one dares to invite Mr. Hua, right?
Not sociable.
It's true that I'm not as pleasant as Mr. Sheng.
I didn't know you flattered
I'm telling you the truth.
Flattery isn't my strength.
But for Mr. Sheng, I can learn.
When's the lesson?
Mm.
Maybe this week
I'll prioritize it.
Those who admire Mr. Sheng
are more than the cockroaches at the kitchen
I can't slack off.
Disgusting.
Let's go.
Brother, are you on the way now?
Yeah, on my way.
It's okay. Inner ring's jammed now.
Take your time
I'll be waiting.
OK
By the way, bringing a plus-one.
Who is it?
What's wrong? Is it awkward?
Not really.
Thought it'd be nice.
We've barely dined alone.
It's a rare opportunity.
Then who's coming.
It can't be Chen Pinming, can it?
No.
Your future in-law.
Can you drive?
Me? Hello?
I'm not talking to you.
We'll be there in half an hour.
Order first.
Why brake so hard?
The red light.
Mr. Sheng claims me.
It's up to you
I'll behave.
You're not doing so well right now.
Really?
Hmph.
Mr. Hua volunteered to drive.
But drives terribly.
I seldom drive.
But if Mr. Sheng wants to.
I‘ll learn.
Idiot.
Why did you put up the inhibitor patch?
And a pheromone spray from Omega.
First impressions matter.
He's not that fragile.
Brother.
Mm.
This must be my future in-law?
You've got a good taste.
Let me.
Please, sit.
Why did you pick this place?
Trendy spot lately.
A viral Restaurant.
Didn't want crowds interrupting.
So I just booked this place.
Invest that money properly.
Yeah, you're right.
Ordered yet?
All set.
Want anything else??
Shouldn't we ask them to add more?
No, this is fine.
Alright.
Waiter, serves the dishes.
I'm sorry.
What's going on?
Scram.
Unbelievable.
Doesn't matter.
Tonight
I brought a special bottle.
Romanee Conti, 1990
I've been thinking.
We've never shared a drink.
Don't be upset by these people.
Just enjoy ourselves.
Mm.
Come on, eat up.
I told you to stay home
had to tag along.
Is it good?
Yeah, it's delicious.
Then have more.
Don't worry, Mr. Sheng.
I won't starve with you around.
Don't just eat your vegetables.
Don't just nibble.
Come on.
My pleasure to see you.
Sorry
I don't drink.
Then learn.
Mr. Hua.
To join the Sheng family
you must drink.
Then to enter Mr. Sheng's life
must I drink?
It's okay.
Why don't you just let brother drink for you?
How can that be?
If Mr. Sheng is drunk
I'd be worried.
Stop making excuses.
Brother, Omegas rarely drink.
Omega.
Mr. Hua, is that right?
If Mr. Sheng said so.
Go on, go on.
Keep going.
Don't stop.
Mr. Sheng.
You're drunk.
Sister-in-law, is my wine bad?
You refuse to drink?
I don't drink.
Then learn.
Listen.
An Omega like you
will have plenty of chances to wait on others while they drink.
Drink this.
Drink up.
Swallow.
What are you doing?
You wouldn't drink with me.
Look down on me?
It's pretty good.
What do you want?
What?
Guess.
What do I want?
Damn useless fools.
Took my money
but still failed to remove his glands.
No choice then
I'll have to do it myself.
My dear brother.
Born with superior glands
he treats us like trash.
S-Class Alpha.
I wonder.
If he doesn't have this gland
what would he be?
But, you.
Don't be afraid.
Without him.
You still have me.
You're not Omega.
Mr. Sheng, you saw it.
He attacked first.
It was self-defense.
It's impossible.
How can that be?
Gland removal is fatal.
No one survives that.
How can you be okay?
What's impossible?
You're lower than a roach
sharing blood with Mr. Sheng is a travesty.
Nothing more absurd.
You could be Mr. Sheng's brother.
What else is impossible?
Shameless.
How dare you?
Without him, you still have me.
I don't need you.
Save you for New Year's dinner?
Listen.
Only Sheng Shaoyou deserves my wrath.
Run, if you value your life.
Seeing as you're a brother-in-law
I've spared you so far.
But you want Mr. Sheng dead.
And damaged my glands.
It hurts.
So now, Shaoqing
you'll pay dearly.
Get out of the way!
B and C-Class Alphas
plus two Betas.
Murder's illegal.
Mr. Sheng won't be happy.
Pathetic.
Barely worth my effort.
Can you do me a favor?
Step aside
I'll teach Sheng Shaoqing a lesson.
A small one, I promise.
Any volunteers?
No takers?
In a rush?
Where are you going?
Do you need any help?
Get lost.
Hello, Secretary General.
Secretary Gao.
After all these years working together.
It's really hard to switch titles overnight.
It's okay, Secretary General.
What can I do for you?
An former colleague retired
we usually throw a farewell.
You've been having gastroenteritis lately
not at your best.
Let me know when you recover.
We'll treat you to dinner.
Yeah, okay.
Thank you, Secretary General.
Gao Tu.
Where are my black cufflinks?
Left cabinet in the break room.
Second drawer.
Oh, thank you.
No problem.
So when will you.
Marry that Omega in heat?
I'm sorry It's private.
What privacy?
Just asking for a date.
Why are you so sensitive?
Privacy my ass.
What does your Omega look like?
Do you have a picture?
Send it to me.
I'm sorry, no.
Who doesn't take photos.
Gao Tu.
When did you become so petty?
Stop ignoring me, Gao Tu.
Why guard an Omega so fiercely?